http://www.rainbowweddingnetwork.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
The following Privacy Policy explains RainbowWeddingNetwork.com's commitment to protecting the privacy of our users and ensuring the integrity of our web sites. By using our sites, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page and will be effective the date the changes are posted. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use this site.
RainbowWeddingNetwork.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-RainbowWeddingNetwork.com web sites to which this or any of our other web sites may link or be linked.
Other than anonymous, aggregate data, when you are on RainbowWeddingNetwork.com's web sites, and do not choose to type in your own personal information, details about your online identity are not collected nor shared with any third party.
If you do choose to register through any of RainbowWeddingNetwork.com's web sites for event tickets, or for a giveaway, honeymoon registry or couples' webpage, or to advertise your business through our marketing portals, your personal and/or professional information will be retained by RainbowWeddingNetwork.com and may be shared with the following entities.
You must refer to their terms of use and privacy policies for other pertinent information.
HoneymoonWishes.com;
Exhibiting companies who participate in the LGBT Wedding Expo for which you have registered for event tickets;
Select Travel Companies and other Wedding Professionals who may further contact you regarding your upcoming Ceremony, Honeymoon or Home & Family planning;
Select Wedding and related Companies that may contact you professionally regarding other marketing opportunities;
Paypal and other credit card processing companies (for online purchases only).
RainbowWeddingNetwork.com, its partners, and affiliates may collect personal information necessary to respond to your requests for our services and to allow you to use the personalized resources available on our website. Personal information includes, but is not limited to, name, physical address, email address, phone number, age and any other information that itself identifies, or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual. RainbowWeddingNetwork.com, its partners, and affiliates may also collect information related to your wedding, including dates and places of the rehearsal, wedding and reception, and information relating to your gift registry and honeymoon. RainbowWeddingNetwork.com recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of the information you choose to provide.
Security:
To protect the security of all data, including our users personal information, RainbowWeddingNetwork.com's
servers are hosted in a secured physical and network environment and efforts are made to secure web servers, networks, host operating systems and databases against unauthorized access. Please remember that the security measures taken by RainbowWeddingNetwork.com are not foolproof; no web site can guarantee that information will be protected in all situations. However, RainbowWeddingNetwork.com can guarantee that it will take all appropriate industry standard measures to protect the information that you provide to us. By submitting any information through our web sites, you are implicitly agreeing to these terms.
Public Domain:
Companies that choose to advertise with RainbowWeddingNetwork.com will find that any and all information they choose to post in our Online Directory, on web banners, in our printed publications (including Show Guides), or through any other sources related to our web sites, may be picked up by the internet search engines and further shared throughout the internet.
RainbowWeddingNetwork.com can not be held liable for the subsequent sharing or display of such information due to this process; please do not submit your full name and/or full company name or other contact information as an advertiser on this web site if you do not wish it to be shared through the internet, as part of the public domain.
